
<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Category name for phrases [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_phrases">Parks</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for colors [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_colors">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for numbers [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_numbers">Sight</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for family members [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_family">Hotels</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="disneyland">
       Disneyland Park, originally Disneyland, is the first of two theme parks built\n
        at the Disneyland Resort in Anaheim, California, opened on July 17, 1955\n
        It is the only theme park designed and built to completion under the direct\n
        supervision of Walt Disney. It was originally the only attraction on the property;\n
        its official name was changed to Disneyland Park to distinguish it from the expanding \n
        complex in the 1990s. It was the first Disney theme park.</string>
    <string name="griffith">
        With over 4,210 acres of both natural chaparral-covered terrain and landscaped\n
        parkland and picnic areas, Griffith Park is the largest municipal park with\n
        urban wilderness area in the United States. Situated in the eastern Santa \n
        Monica Mountain range, the Parks elevations range from 384 to 1,625 feet\n
        above sea level. With an arid climate, the Parks plant communities vary \n
        from coastal sage scrub, oak and walnut woodlands to riparian vegetation\n
        with trees in the Parks deep canyons.</string>
    <string name="zoo">
        The Los Angeles Zoo was the fourth zoo to serve the city.
        1885: The City-owned Eastlake Zoo opens in East Los Angeles Park.
        1912: The Griffith Park Zoo opens (a few miles from the current\n
        Los Angeles Zoo site) with 15 animals.
        1915: Colonel William Selig opens his combination movie studio\n
        and zoo, the Selig Zoo, in Lincoln Park.
        By 1956, the citizens of Los Angeles realized their city had \n
        outgrown the small Griffith Park Zoo. </string>
    <string name="pacific">
        Pacific Park is an oceanfront amusement park located in Santa\n
        Monica, California. The park, located on the Santa Monica Pier,\n
        looks directly out on the Pacific Ocean, in the direction of\n
        Catalina Island. It is the only amusement park on the West \n
        Coast of the United States located on a pier and LAs only \n
        admission-free park.</string>

    <string name="adventure">
        For little ones who are just getting used to rides—and\n
        for families who want a bite-sized theme park\n
        visit Adventure City is an old-fashioned crowd-pleaser,\n
        with its small rollercoasters, a 1946 carousel and\n
        the chance to create your own train track design.
        </string>
    <string name="raging">
        Raging Waters Los Angeles is California’s best and\n
        largest waterpark! This 60-acre waterpark in the\n
        Los Angeles area has been recognized by USA Today\n
        as a Top 10 Water Park and is home to more than \n
        50 world-class rides
        </string>
    <string name="knotts">
        Fun is always in season at Knotts Berry Farm! With dozens of rides,\n
        roller coasters, attractions in five themed areas, there is\n
        something for everyone!
        </string>
    <string name="traktir">
        Cuisine: Eastern European
        </string>
    <string name="nnaka">
        Cuisine: Japanese
        </string>
    <string name="providence">
        Cuisine: Seafood restaurant
        </string>
    <string name="above">
        Cuisine: American
        </string>
    <string name="premier">
        Cuisine: Russian
        </string>
    <string name="catchla">
        Cuisine: American
        </string>
    <string name="ush">
    Universal Studios Hollywood is a film studio and theme park in the San Fernando\n
        Valley area of Los Angeles County, California. About 70% of the studio lies \n
        within the unincorporated county island known as Universal City while the \n
        rest lies within the city limits of Los Angeles, California. It is one of \n
        the oldest and most famous Hollywood film studios still in use. Its official\n
        marketing headline is The Entertainment Capital of LA.
        </string>
    <string name="griffitho">
       Southern California’s gateway to the cosmos! Visitors can look through telescopes,\n
        explore exhibits, see live shows in the Samuel Oschin Planetarium, and enjoy\n
        spectacular views of Los Angeles and the Hollywood Sign.
        </string>
    <string name="hollywood">
        The Hollywood Sign is a memorial sign in the Hollywood Hills in Los Angeles,\n
        California. It is the word "HOLLYWOOD" written in large white letters.\n
        The mark was created as an advertisement in 1923, but later became widely\n
        known as the trademark of the US film industry.
        </string>
    <string name="museum">
        The Los Angeles County Museum of Art is a US art museum located in Los Angeles,\n
        California. The largest art museum in the western United States, visited\n
        by over a million people annually. It is included in the hundred most\n
        visited art museums in the world.
        </string>
    <string name="walt">
       The Walt Disney Concert Hall is Los Angeles newest concert \n
        venue, home to the Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra. Opened October 23, 2003.
        </string>
    <string name="natural">
        Los Angeles County Natural History Museum, eng. The Natural History Museum of \n
        Los AngelesCounty is located at Exposition Park in Los Angeles, California, USA.
        </string>
    <string name="petersen">
       The Petersen Automotive Museum is located on Wilshire Boulevard along\n
        Museum Row in the Miracle Mile neighborhood of Los Angeles. One of\n
        the worlds largest automotive museums, the Petersen Automotive Museum\n
        is a nonprofit organization specializing in automobile history and \n
        related educational programs.
        </string>
    <string name="ritz">
       500-600$
        </string>
    <string name="beverly">
       900-1200$
        </string>
    <string name="freeland">
       150-350$
        </string>
    <string name="wald">
       700-1000$
        </string>
    <string name="four">
       600-1200$
        </string>
    <string name="jw">
       200-1000$
        </string>
    <string name="wilshire">
       600-1100$
        </string>
</resources>
